<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Physiotherapy Douma in Hilversum: Your physiotherapist nearby on Physiotherapy Douma</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/</link><description>Recent content in Physiotherapy Douma in Hilversum: Your physiotherapist nearby on Physiotherapy Douma</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Physiotherapy after COVID-19</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/covid19-physiotherapy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 12:52:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/covid19-physiotherapy/</guid><description>Physiotherapy for recovery after COVID-19 An infection with the Coronavirus (COVID-19) can have a significant impact on your health. It is important to start physiotherapy as soon as possible after hospitalization. Even if you have not been admitted to hospital, guidance by a physiotherapist may be necessary because you have been inactive for a long time.
Make appointment Home / En / Physiotherapy after COVID-19 🇳🇱 Even if you have not been admitted to hospital, guidance by a physiotherapist may be necessary because you have been inactive for a long time.</description></item><item><title>Specialisations of Physiotherapy Douma Hilversum</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/specialisations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/specialisations/</guid><description> Specialisations of Physiotherapy Douma Hilversum Physiotherapy Dizziness Pelvic physiotherapy Manual therapy Geriatric Physiotherapy Pysiotherapy after COVID-19 Meer specialisaties van Fysiotherapie Douma Edema Therapy Jaw Physiotherapy Dry Needling Acupuncture Orthopaedic Revalidation Medical Taping Business Fitness Acquired brain injuries Pregnancy-fit and Mom-fit Parkinsons</description></item><item><title>Opening Hours</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/opening-hours/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 12:24:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/opening-hours/</guid><description>Opening hours Fysiotherapie Douma **Day** **Opening hours** Monday 07:00 - 21:00 Tuesday 07:00 - 17:00 Wednesday 07:00 - 17:00 Thursday 07:00 - 21:00 Friday 07:00 - 17:00 Saturday 08:00 - 13:00 Sunday Closed</description></item><item><title>Medical Taping Treatment</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/medical-taping-treatment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 12:02:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/medical-taping-treatment/</guid><description>Medical Taping Treatment Medical taping is a treatment method in which muscle activity is used to help recovery after injuries. Muscles aid blood flow and the draining of waste substances through the body.
Make an appointment Home / En / Medical Taping Treatment Medical taping uses elastic tapes which support muscles without obstructing them. The muscle activity improves tissue blood flow and so aids recovery.
Medical tape vs.</description></item><item><title>Orthopaedic Revalidation</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/orthopaedic-revalidation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 13:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/orthopaedic-revalidation/</guid><description>Orthopaedic Revalidation Revalidation after a knee- hip-, or shoulder injury.
Make an appointment Home / En / Orthopaedic Revalidation Orthopaedic revalidation is suitable for patients which have undergone an orthopaedic operation in the hospital. You can also be directly referred to a physiotherapist by an orthopaedic surgeon, without an operation. Common orthopaedic operations include hip- and knee operations such as total hip prosthesis, and posterior cruciate ligament-, meniscus-, or viewing operations.</description></item><item><title>Medical fitness</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/medical-fitness/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 12:22:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/medical-fitness/</guid><description>Medical Fitness In addition to physiotherapy, also exercise in Hilversum under expert supervision
Make an appointment Home / En / Medical fitness More about medical fitness Medical fitness helps maintain or improve your health. To have enough energy for your daily life, you might want to improve your condition or lose weight, but not in a crowded fitness centrum surrounded by top-fit athletes. In the practices of Physiotherapy Douma, we understand this.</description></item><item><title>Business Fitness</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/business-fitness/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 11:26:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/business-fitness/</guid><description>On average, this increases the work productivity by 12,5% and decreases absences by 2%.
More about the business-fitness scan Many businesses wrestle with high absence rates and low work productivity. An important factor in this is the health and wellbeing of the employees. The business-fitness scan doesn&amp;rsquo;t look at the absence rates in the business but at the wellbeing of the employees (or lack thereof). We combine this with a general health scan of the company as a whole.</description></item><item><title>Acquired brain injuries</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/acquired-brain-injuries/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 11:17:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/acquired-brain-injuries/</guid><description>Acquired brain injuries Brain injury that has occurred after birth, for example as a result of an accident.
Make an appointment Home / En / Acquired brain injuries More about acquired brain injuries (ABI) Physiotherapy Douma has strong connections to the category of patients with an acquired brain injury. Acquired brain injuries, or ABI, refers too injuries which have been dealt to the brain during a person&amp;rsquo;s life.</description></item><item><title>Pregnancy-fit and Mom-fit</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/pregnancy-fit-and-mom-fit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 11:02:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/pregnancy-fit-and-mom-fit/</guid><description>Pregnancy-fit and Mom-fit Are you looking for an active lesson to keep exercising during and after pregnancy and do you also want some more information about this period and what comes after it? Then Pregnancy-fit and Mom-fit is something for you!
Make an appointment Home / En / Pregnancy-fit and Mom-fit Pregnancy-fit / Mom-fit is a contemporary cursus for women who are pregnant or have recently given birth.</description></item><item><title>ParkinsonsNet</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/parkinsons/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 12:44:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/parkinsons/</guid><description>ParkinsonsNet The network for healthcare providers for Parkinson&amp;rsquo;s patients.
Make an appointment Home / En / ParkinsonsNet ParkinsonNet is a national network of healthcare providers which are specialised in treating and assisting Parkinson patients.
More than 2700 healthcare providers (neurologists, occupational therapists, logopaedics, and nurses, among others) are connected to this network.
The goal of ParkinsonNet is to provide the very best healthcare possible to everyone with Parkinson&amp;rsquo;s disease or an atypical parkinsonism.</description></item><item><title>Pelvic physiotherapy</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/pelvic-physiotherapy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 12:33:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/pelvic-physiotherapy/</guid><description>Pelvic physiotherapy Pelvic physiotherapy is focused on improving the function of the muscles in and around the pelvis.
Make an appointment Home / En / Pelvic physiotherapy Indications for pelvic physiotherapy Loss of urine, needing to urinate abnormally often Loss of defecation or flatulence, abnormal need to use the bathroom, constipation Pain during sex Diastasis Pain in the pelvic floor Women: prolapse, pelvic pain during pregnancy Men: erection- and ejaculation problems Are you affected by one of these afflictions?</description></item><item><title>Dizziness</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/dizziness/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 12:16:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/dizziness/</guid><description>Dizziness Dizziness can express itself in many forms. What you feel as a patient can differ from person to person.
Make an appointment Home / En / Dizziness More about dizziness You might feel like you&amp;rsquo;re floating; as if the world is spinning around you, or as if you are turning around yourself. Sometimes you forget where you are and have the feeling you are falling down.</description></item><item><title>Acupuncture treatment in Hilversum - Make an appointment</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/acupuncture/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 14:26:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/acupuncture/</guid><description>Acupuncture treatment in Hilversum A widely used medicine (especially in China) in which needles are inserted into the subcutaneous connective tissue at very specific points.
Make an appointment Home / En / Acupuncture treatment in Hilversum - Make an appointment 🇳🇱 Acupuncture treatment in Hilversum? Do you need acupuncture treatment, because you can&amp;rsquo;t get rid of chronic or acute afflictions? Then the Physiotherapy Douma&amp;rsquo;s acupuncturist will gladly help you.</description></item><item><title>Dry Needling in Hilversum?</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/dry-needling-hilversum/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 13:54:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/dry-needling-hilversum/</guid><description>Dry Needling Hilversum Dry needling is a treatment method whereby a very thin needle is inserted into the skin and muscle.
Make an appointment Home / En / Dry Needling in Hilversum? Dry needling is very effective against myofascial pain and triggerpoints. Triggerpoints are tiny areas of hardened tissue in muscles, which can cause radiating pain issues. &amp;lsquo;Dry&amp;rsquo; indicates that nothing is injected through the needle; it is only use to puncture the triggerpoint.</description></item><item><title>Jaw physiotherapy in Hilversum with 40+ years of experience</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/jaw-physiotherapy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 12:09:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/jaw-physiotherapy/</guid><description>Jaw physiotherapy The most important components of the jaw are the jaw joint, the teeth, and the chewing muscles.
Make an appointment Home / En / Jaw physiotherapy in Hilversum with 40&amp;#43; years of experience More about jaw physiotherapy The most common symptoms of jaw- or facial problems are:
Pain or tiredness in the chewing muscles Trouble with opening one&amp;rsquo;s mouth Pain in or around the jaw joints (in front of the ears) Snapping or creaking jaw joints Overly sensitive or painful teeth Abnormal erosion of the teeth Ear pain Headaches Neck pain If you recognise one or more of these symptoms, there is a chance that you are suffering from facial problems.</description></item><item><title>Geriatric Physiotherapy</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/geriatric-physiotherapy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 13:40:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/geriatric-physiotherapy/</guid><description>Geriatric Physiotherapy in Hilversum Geriatrics is the medical specialisation which busies itself with the treatment of the elderly and those who, due to illness, show symptoms of advanced age (due to for example Parkinson’s or rheumatoid arthritis).
Make an appointment Home / En / Geriatric Physiotherapy More about geriatric physiotherapy Geriatrics does not only concern itself with afflictions related to for example problematic memory issues or dementia, but also with the whole: all (bodily and mental) afflictions and issues.</description></item><item><title>Physiotherapy in Hilversum</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/physiotherapy-in-hilversum/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 13:14:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/physiotherapy-in-hilversum/</guid><description>Physiotherapy in Hilversum Looking for a trustworthy physiotherapist in Hilversum? Physiotherapy Douma is glad to be of your assistance. Our therapists treat you with personal attention and a smile.
Make an appointment Home / En / Physiotherapy in Hilversum Make an appointment with Physiotherapy Douma Physiotherapy Douma employs experienced physiotherapists, each with their own specialisations. Physiotherapy focuses on afflictions related to movement of the body. We treat your affliction with various methods.</description></item><item><title>Edema therapy</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/edema-therapy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 11:25:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/edema-therapy/</guid><description>Edema therapy The lymph nodes lie close to major organs and contain the janitors and policemen of the bloodstream, the white blood cells. Due to a disturbed balance between the supplying and draining of moisture an abnormal accumulation of moisture can develop, also known as an oedema.
Make an appointment Home / En / Edema therapy More about edema therapy Problems in the lymphatic system can be congenital (primary lymph oedema), but usually lymph oedema occurs as a result of severe damage to the lymph nodes or lymph vessels (secondary lymph edema).</description></item><item><title>Manual therapy Hilversum</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/manual-therapy-hilversum/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 11:07:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/manual-therapy-hilversum/</guid><description>Manual therapy The goal of manual therapy is on the one hand the improvement of the functioning of the joints and on the other hand the improvement of posture and movement. To achieve this, the manual therapist uses a number of specific techniques which can be applied in the joints.
Make an appointment Home / En / Manual therapy Hilversum More about manual therapy The effects of manual therapy are often immediately noticeable; you experience improved freedom of movement and a decrease in pain.</description></item><item><title>Employees</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/employees/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 13:09:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/employees/</guid><description>Employees at Physiotherapy Douma</description></item><item><title>Make an appointment</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/appointment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 13:43:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/appointment/</guid><description>Make an appointment Via the form you can easily register for a physiotherapy appointment at our practice. Once we have received this form, we will call you within 1 working day to make an appointment.
This form is sent via a secure SSL connection (see the padlock in the address bar) and can therefore not be intercepted by third parties.</description></item><item><title>Physiotherapy practices in Hilversum</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/location/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 13:16:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/location/</guid><description>[et_pb_section fb_built=&amp;ldquo;1&amp;rdquo; admin_label=&amp;ldquo;section&amp;rdquo; _builder_version=&amp;ldquo;3.22.3&amp;rdquo;][et_pb_row admin_label=&amp;ldquo;Rij&amp;rdquo; _builder_version=&amp;ldquo;3.25&amp;rdquo; background_size=&amp;ldquo;initial&amp;rdquo; background_position=&amp;ldquo;top_left&amp;rdquo; background_repeat=&amp;ldquo;repeat&amp;rdquo;][et_pb_column type=&amp;ldquo;4_4&amp;rdquo; _builder_version=&amp;ldquo;3.25&amp;rdquo; custom_padding=&amp;quot;|||&amp;quot; custom_padding__hover=&amp;quot;|||&amp;quot;][et_pb_text admin_label=&amp;ldquo;Intro&amp;rdquo; _builder_version=&amp;ldquo;3.26.5&amp;rdquo; background_size=&amp;ldquo;initial&amp;rdquo; background_position=&amp;ldquo;top_left&amp;rdquo; background_repeat=&amp;ldquo;repeat&amp;rdquo; use_border_color=&amp;ldquo;off&amp;rdquo; border_color=&amp;quot;#ffffff&amp;quot; border_style=&amp;ldquo;solid&amp;rdquo;]
Physiotherapy practices in Hilversum Looking for a physical therapist near you in Hilversum, Noord-Holland? Then contact the nearest location of Physiotherapy Douma. We have three locations spread throughout Hilversum.[/et_pb_text][/et_pb_column][/et_pb_row][et_pb_row column_structure=&amp;ldquo;1_2,1_2&amp;rdquo; admin_label=&amp;ldquo;Rij&amp;rdquo; _builder_version=&amp;ldquo;3.25&amp;rdquo; background_size=&amp;ldquo;initial&amp;rdquo; background_position=&amp;ldquo;top_left&amp;rdquo; background_repeat=&amp;ldquo;repeat&amp;rdquo;][et_pb_column type=&amp;ldquo;1_2&amp;rdquo; _builder_version=&amp;ldquo;3.25&amp;rdquo; custom_padding=&amp;quot;|||&amp;quot; custom_padding__hover=&amp;quot;|||&amp;quot;][et_pb_text admin_label=&amp;ldquo;Zuiderheide&amp;rdquo; _builder_version=&amp;ldquo;3.26.5&amp;rdquo; background_size=&amp;ldquo;initial&amp;rdquo; background_position=&amp;ldquo;top_left&amp;rdquo; background_repeat=&amp;ldquo;repeat&amp;rdquo; use_border_color=&amp;ldquo;off&amp;rdquo; border_color=&amp;quot;#ffffff&amp;quot; border_style=&amp;ldquo;solid&amp;rdquo;]
Physiotherapy Douma &amp;ldquo;Main Location&amp;rdquo; Diependaalselaan 337A</description></item><item><title>Practice information</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/about-us/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 14:39:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/about-us/</guid><description>About us Physiotherapy Douma is a physiotherapy practice with three locations in the south of Hilversum.
Make an appointment Home / En / Practice information We stand for Personal attention Goal-focused care Customer satisfaction Guaranteed high quality treatment More about our practices Our practice always works with the newest insights and regulations in physiotherapy, and we are audited yearly.</description></item><item><title>Fysiotherapie Douma Hilversum</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/fysiotherapie-douma-hilversum/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 14:19:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/en/fysiotherapie-douma-hilversum/</guid><description>Do you need physiotherapy in Hilversum? We&amp;rsquo;re always nearby For all physiotherapy in Hilversum you can go to Physical Therapy Douma. With 3 locations in Hilversum, there is always a location near you. The physiotherapists at Fysiotherapie Douma all have their own specialization and, if necessary, come to the entire Gooi area. Never been with us? No problem! We look forward to receiving you in one of our physiotherapy practices.</description></item><item><title>Medisch Fitness Training</title><link>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/medisch-fitness-training/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 10:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.fysiodouma.nl/medisch-fitness-training/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>